Here we are, G2 taking on Vitality.
这里是 G2 对阵 Vitality。
Yes, here we go.
好的，比赛开始。
Semi-finals on the line, quarter-finals for the losers.
半决赛资格在此一战，败者落入四分之一决赛。
G2 versus Vitality, and we are finally ready to go here.
G2 对阵 Vitality，我们终于准备开打了。
On Mirage, CT-side start for Team Vitality.
Mirage 这张图，Vitality 先做 CT。
T-side start here for G2.
G2 这边先做 T。
We'll see what huNter- decides to do
看看 huNter- 会怎么处理
with all that utility.
手里的这些道具。
He's got a smoke and a Molotov.
他有一颗烟和一颗燃烧瓶。
We're gonna see ZywOo drop down into the underpass.
我们会看到 ZywOo 跳进地下道。
Now Vitality didn't have a great game
现在，Vitality 昨天整体表现并不好，
as a team yesterday, but ZywOo is still ZywOo, so...
但 ZywOo 还是那个 ZywOo，所以……
It's flameZ to get the start. ZywOo
开局由 flameZ 拿到首杀，ZywOo
looking for the follow-up, and of course
还想继续找后续击杀，当然，
he's got a kill.
他确实拿到了一个人头。
apEX has come through there and nicked one away as well.
apEX 也从那里冲出来，又收掉一个。
And this pistol round has started very strong.
这个手枪局开得非常强势。
Yeah, yeah, Team Vitality.
是啊，是啊，Team Vitality。
I guess the question we haven't really asked yet is
我觉得我们还没真正问过的问题是：
maybe after the performance yesterday:
也许在昨天那场表现之后，
is this the one where Vitality come in
这会不会是 Vitality 进来之后，
and just take out all their anger and frustration
把所有怒火和挫败感
on G2? Lovely shot from flameZ at the start.
都发泄到 G2 身上的一场？flameZ 开局这一枪很漂亮。
And then obviously the apEX-ZywOo aggression.
然后显然还有 apEX 和 ZywOo 的前压。
Well, I was excited to see what huNter- was gonna
我本来很期待看看 huNter-
do with the utility,
会怎么用这些道具，
but it doesn't really matter anymore
但现在已经不重要了。
when you've lost everybody that early into the round.
因为回合这么早，你人就全掉光了。
It's your Plan A's out the window,
你的 A 计划已经没了，
Plan B's out the window,
B 计划也没了，
and you really don't have a plan anymore.
你基本上已经没有计划了。
No, there is no plan.
没错，已经没有计划了。
You're just like,
你现在就像是：
'I'm gonna just keep moving forward
“我就继续往前走，
and see what happens,
看看会发生什么，
and we'll take it,
能打成什么样就打成什么样，
we'll take it every step of the way.'
一步一步来吧。”
Off he goes through the underpass here, huNter-.
huNter- 从地下道往前走。
And that, okay, that wasn't really competitive whatsoever.
好吧，这个回合几乎没有任何对抗性。
So Vitality finding everything
所以 Vitality 拿到了
they could possibly want.
他们想要的一切。
Pistol round goes smoothly.
手枪局顺利拿下。
And no bomb plant, of course, coming in here for G2.
当然，G2 这边也没有下包。
Even so, no force buy
即便如此，下一回合
in the next round.
也不会有强起。
You'd imagine it's gonna be a full eco,
估计会是一个完整 eco，
allowing Vitality a 2-0 lead.
让 Vitality 拿到 2-0 领先。